(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
アンデッドアリス！
Undead Alice!
みんな集まってくれてありがとうございまーす！
Thank you all for coming!
最後まで楽しんでってくれると嬉しいです！
I hope you'll enjoy until the very end!
まずは一曲目行きます！
Here is the first song!
思うようにいかないなら
If things don't go the way you want
私を捨て君は生きて
then cast me aside and live on
狂ってた君の残響は
Even though I can hear the echoes
僕じゃなくたって聴こえるのに
of your madness even without you
自傷は綻ぶたびに
Every time self-harm unravels
幸せ吸って毒を吐いて
inhale happiness and exhale poison
理想じゃ二人のだけが
It feels good knowing that in our ideals,
正常だって気持ちいいじゃんか
only the two of us are normal, right?
合図で誤魔化したい様が
The way you want to deceive with signals
会いたくちゃ不自然だろが
is unnatural when you want to meet
仲良くなっちゃってよ
Let's get along
底冷えドキドキが嫌になって
I'm tired of the bone-chilling palpitations
僕が君を殺す前に
Before I kill you,
死んでくれ
please die
吊るしていてよ　吊るしていてよ
Keep me hanging, keep me hanging
壊していてよ　壊していてよ
Keep breaking me, keep breaking me
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだ　こんなのもうやめよう
Let's forget, let's stop this already
嫌った方が　嫌ってい出ても
Even if the one who hated continues to hate
想った方が　想っていたんじゃんか
The one who loved, loved you after all
もう笑えない僕の
For the me who can no longer smile,
アンデッドアリスへ
to Undead Alice
予想通り僕の夢が
As expected, as my dreams
輝くほど君は陰ってく
shine brighter, you grow darker
犠牲を我慢と呼んで
Calling sacrifice "patience,"
汚れた手で何を回した
what did you spin with those dirty hands?
悪用しないように
So as not to make things worse,
それがつまり悪い形
which essentially is a bad shape
保存状態愛は冷凍で
Preservation state: Love is frozen
何度も温め直すんですか？
Are you going to reheat it over and over?
正しくありたい本能が
The instinct to want to be right
正しくないことの脂肪が
and the fat of being wrong
仲良くなっちゃってよ
let's get along
底冷えハナハナが苦になって
I'm tired of the bone-chilling separation
僕が僕を殺す前に
Before I kill myself,
死んでやる
I'll die
吊るしていてよ　吊るしていてよ
Keep me hanging, keep me hanging
壊していてよ　壊していてよ
Keep breaking me, keep breaking me
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだ　こんなのもうやめよう
Let's forget, let's stop this already
嫌った方が　嫌ってい出ても
Even if the one who hated continues to hate
想った方が　想っていたんじゃんか
The one who loved, loved you after all
もう笑えない僕の
For the me who can no longer smile,
アンデッドアリスへ
to Undead Alice
ずっとこのまま　ふたりで夢を見れるって
That we could keep dreaming together forever...
勝手ばかりで　君はどんな顔で笑っていたっけ
You were so selfish, what kind of face did you have when you smiled?
バイバイしたから　元通りなんて幻想だ
Since we said goodbye, things going back to normal is just an illusion
まあまあツラいじゃん　胸を割いて愛を潰してくれよ
It's pretty painful, so rip open my chest and crush this love
吊るしていてよ　吊るしていてよ
Keep me hanging, keep me hanging
壊していてよ　壊していてよ
Keep breaking me, keep breaking me
卑怯な愛はここに埋めよう
Let's bury this cowardly love here
忘れるんだ　こんなのもうやめよう
Let's forget, let's stop this already
嫌った方が　嫌ってい出ても
Even if the one who hated continues to hate
想った方が　想っていたんじゃんか
The one who loved, loved you after all
もう笑えない僕の
For the me who can no longer smile,
アンデッドアリスへ
to Undead Alice
痛いくらいで　消えそうもないや
It hurts so much, but it won't disappear
地獄くらいじゃ　消えそうもないや
Even hell won't make it disappear
「ごめんね」なんて　言えるはずないな
I could never say "I'm sorry"
密かな期待なんて　叶えられないなんて
That secret expectations could never be fulfilled...
違うじゃないか　違うじゃないか
That's not it, that's not it
死ねない想いは　火にまかせるのか
Will I leave these feelings that won't die to the flames?
もう笑えない僕の
For the me who can no longer smile,
アンデッドアリスへ
to Undead Alice
まだまだお披露目続くから
The showcase is still going on,
最後まで見ていってね！
so stay tuned until the very end!
それではここからは
Now, from here
スペシャルな動画があるから
we have a special video, so...
見ていってください！
Please watch!
ラプラス・ダークネス Vlog in 京都
La+ Darknesss Vlog in Kyoto
京都着いた。
I've arrived in Kyoto.
めっちゃ人で...
There are so many people...
てか、でけぇ！
And wow, it's huge!
あ、逃げた。待って。
Ah, they ran away. Wait.
ちょっと鳩いる。
There are some pigeons.
暑い...
It's hot...
ね...
Right...
暑いよね...
It's hot, isn't it?
見て、雲ないかも。
Look, there might not be any clouds.
ね。
Yeah.
ほら来た。
Here we go.
何食べようかな。
What should I eat?
何食べる？
What are you having?
釜飯よね。
Kamameshi, right.
えっと、ハンバーグ。
Um, hamburger steak.
絶対ハンバーグにするわ。
I'm definitely getting the hamburger steak.
来た！
It's here!
え、めっちゃ美味しそう。
Wow, it looks so delicious.
な、これ。
Look at this.
めっちゃ美味しそう。
It looks so delicious.
泣いてるんですな。
It's sizzling!
お、健康そう。
Oh, it looks healthy.
いいね。
Nice.
食べた。
I finished it.
美味しかった。
It was delicious.
食べた？
Did you eat?
でっか！
It's huge!
あ、吾輩ここ食べる。
Ah, I'll eat this part.
この餅。
This mochi.
あと苺。
And the strawberry.
半分個しよう。
Let's share it.
お腹いっぱい。
I'm full.
めっちゃお腹いっぱい。
I'm really full.
食べた。
I finished it.
よく食べたね。
We really ate a lot, didn't we?
あー、もう無理。
Ah, I can't eat anymore.
すごい
Wow
こっち見て
Look this way
かわいい
Cute
あ、ケータイ落としそう
Ah, I might drop my phone
鳥
A bird
じーん...
Staring...
おー
Oh
何してるの？
What are you doing?
鳥
Bird
はっ
Ah
うわー
Whoa
日が沈むのって時間かかるのね
It takes time for the sun to set, doesn't it?
いつまで見てんの
How long are you going to watch?
もう沈むやろ これ ほぼ
It's about to set now. Almost.
ほぼ沈んだね
It's almost set.
うわ、すご
Wow, amazing
「和」を感じる
I feel the "wa" (Japanese spirit).
お風呂だ！
It's a bathtub!
あ、お風呂だ
Ah, a bathtub.
外にもお風呂だ
There's a bathtub outside too.
すごーい
Amazing.
あ、タワー！
Ah, the tower!
すごい
Wow.
これ何？
What's this?
トイレ！
Toilet!
ベッド！
Bed!
吾輩の手前、絶対。
This one's mine, for sure.
うりゃー！
Urya-!
何頼んだの？
What did you order?
「稼ぎ頭」？
“Kasegi-gashira”?
おもろすぎ
That's too funny.
お前はね、むしろ...
You, rather...
飲んでみたい
I want to try drinking it.
一口ちょうだい
Give me a sip.
おいで
Come here.
うわー
Uwah...
アルコールだぜ
It's alcohol!
うわ、高そー、何これ。
Whoa, looks expensive! What is this?
ハモの... 焼きつけ三種。
Pike conger... Three kinds of grilled...
どれが三種なんだ。
Which one makes the three?
わ、肉来た。高そー。
Wow, the meat's here! Looks expensive.
わさび。食べます。
Wasabi. I'm going to eat it.
食べ終わった。
I've finished eating.
美味しかったけど、冷たかった。
It was delicious, but it was cold.
お腹いっぱいだね。眠い。
I'm full. I'm sleepy.
おはよー。
Good morning!
起きて。起きてー。
Wake up. Wake up!
おいしそー。
Looks delicious!
食べたい。食べていい？
I want to eat. Can I eat?
ごちそうさまでした。
Thank you for the meal.
お腹いっぱい。
I'm full.
これ、ホテルにあったやつ。
This is the one that was in the hotel.
これ欲しかったんだ。
I wanted this.
これ、昨日飲んでたやつ。
This is the one I was drinking yesterday.
買うちゃお。
I'm gonna buy it.
やばい、間に合うかしら。
Oh no, will I make it in time?
間に合うか。
Will I make it?
何も用意してない。
I haven't prepared anything.
おい、手伝えお前。
Hey, you! Help me out.
もう用意終わったの？
Are you finished with the preparations already?
たとえば今君が その瞳 濡らしていたとしてもう
For example, even if you were wetting those eyes right now,
呼ぶ声はもう聞こえない
The voice that calls out can no longer be heard.
永遠の雲を解かすように 君との日々は
Like dissolving eternal clouds, the days spent with you
記憶の中に滲んでいく
Begin to bleed into my memories.
何かを求めれば 何かが
If you seek something, something else
零れ落ちていく
Spills and falls away.
そんなこの世界で
In a world like this.
春の風を待つあの花のように
Like that flower waiting for the spring breeze,
君という光があるのなら
If a light called "you" exists,
巡り巡る運命を越えて
Crossing over the cycling fate,
咲かせるさ 愛の花を
I will make the flowers of love bloom.
花束を
A bouquet of them.
願いが叶うのなら 二人の世界 また生きてみたい
If my wish could come true, I'd want to live in our world once again.
あの日から芽吹く日々
The days that have sprouted since that day.
水色 花びらはもう 香りを忘れ
The light blue petals have already forgotten their scent,
君への思い枯れていく
My feelings for you are withering away.
満ちてしまいそうな心に
In a heart that seems like it might overflow,
覚えたての愛の美しさを
The beauty of a love just newly learned...
ねぇ 咲かせて
Hey, make it bloom.
春の風を待つあの花のように
Like that flower waiting for the spring breeze,
飾らない心でいられたら
If only I could stay with an unadorned heart,
触れられない でも想い煩う
I can't touch you, but I still worry and pine.
忘れないよ この恋を
I won't forget this love.
ひとつずつ束ねて
Binding them together one by one,
君という light があるのなら
If a light called "you" exists,
巡り巡る運命を越えて
Crossing over the cycling fate,
咲かせるさ 愛の花を
I will make the flowers of love bloom.
花束を
A bouquet of them.
目指せ100万円！ホロライブ激辛王決定戦！
Aim for 1 million yen! Hololive Extremely Spicy King Deciding Match!
司会は私、holoXの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイがね、お送りさせていただきます。
I, the female executive of holoX, Takane Lui, will be your host today.
今日、100万円を目指して激辛を喰らう猛者たちがここに集まってくださいました。
Today, the brave souls who will eat extremely spicy food to aim for 1 million yen have gathered here.
一人ずつ自己紹介してもらいましょうか。
Let's have them introduce themselves one by one.
ワーカホリックにスパイスは必須！
Spice is a must for a workaholic!
ということでホロライブスタッフの友人Aです。よろしくお願いしますー。
And so, I'm Hololive staff member Yuujin A. Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いしますー
Pleased to be here!
いえーい
Yay!
100万円、食べます
I'm going to eat 1 million yen.
ラプラス・ダークネスです
I'm La+ Darknesss.
よろしく〜
Nice to meet you!
えー、辛味と寝ました。白上フブキです
Uh, I slept with spiciness. I'm Shirakami Fubuki.
よろしくお願いしまーす
Please treat me well!
ここ！辛味でーす
Here! It's the spiciness!
お願いしまーす！
Thank you!
好きなカレーは子供用のバターチキンだ…
My favorite curry is child's butter chicken...
でも麦ジュースがあれば何とか解決できる！って
But if there's barley juice, I can manage somehow!
エロい人も言ってる。
That's what the naughty person said.
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
なんか不思議なメンバーが集まりましたが
A strange group of members has gathered...
え、ラプラスなんでこの4人になったの？
Wait, La+, why did it end up being these four?
そうだ、確かに
That's true, actually.
なんかフブキさんとえーちゃんさんは
Well, Fubuki-san and A-chan-san...
辛いの好きなの知ってるけど
I know they like spicy food, so...
なんか面白そうだなと思って呼んで
I thought it would be interesting and invited them.
で、アキロゼさんは雑魚だけど
And Aki-rose-san is a weakling, but...
おいおいおいお前！
Hey hey hey, you!
雑魚って言ったな！
You called me a weakling!
お前も雑魚だろうが！
You're a weakling too!
なんかいい勝負できそうだなって思って
I thought we could have a good match.
なるほど、なるほどね
I see, I see.
足の引っ張り合いが始まるんだ
The mutual dragging down begins.
絶対負けない！
I won't lose!
100万円はラブちゃんからの、holoXからの資金ということですね
So the 1 million yen is from La-chan... funds from holoX.
まあそれはね、あの、貰ってからのお楽しみだよね
Well, that's, uh, something to look forward to after receiving it.
いやー楽しみだなー！
Man, I'm looking forward to it!
holoXからのポケットマネーで
With pocket money from holoX...
あーちょっとちょっとやめてくださいそれは
Ah, hey, hey, please stop that.
食う飯はうまいぞー！
The food we eat will be delicious!
ルイ、よろしく！
I'm Lui, please be kind!
ということでね
And so...
この4人の熱い勇士と戦う料理を紹介いたしましょう
Let me introduce the dishes that these four brave warriors will fight.
来い！ルイ
Come! Lui.
はい
Yes.
ちょっとねーなんかすごい、結構辛そう
Wait, it looks... really quite spicy.
そう辛いんだよね
Yes, it's spicy.
ちょっとね、皆さんにはお見せできないのが残念なくらい
It's so much that it's a shame I can't show it to everyone...
本当に辛そうなんですけれども
It really looks spicy.
比較のために、辛くないものも用意していただいたので
For comparison, I also had non-spicy ones prepared.
あ、そうなんか2つあるんだけど
Ah, I see, there are two of them.
辛くない方からちょっと食べてみましょう
Let's try the non-spicy one first.
はい、じゃあルイ、あーん
Okay, now Lui, say "ahh".
はーい、あーん
Okay, "ahh".
んー！おいしい！
Mmm! Delicious!
あーいいですね、かわいいかわいい
Ah, that's good. Cute, cute.
で、こっちが辛い方らしい
And this is supposedly the spicy one.
辛いやつ…あーなんか赤いな…
The spicy one... Ah, it looks red...
はい、あーん。いただきます
Okay, "ahh". Let's eat.
ん？変わんない？
Hmm? No change?
うそー！！
No way!!
待て待て、吾輩匂い嗅いでるからわかるけど明らかににおかしいんだよねこっち
Wait, wait. I can tell because I'm smelling it, but this one is clearly weird.
企画倒れになっちゃうからおなじだったら！
It'll be a project failure if it's the same!
ちょ、おまえ、いやマジあの、お前バケモンだよ、バケモン
Wait, you... No, seriously, you're a monster, a monster.
そんなはずない！
That can't be!
全然辛くないんだけど
It's not spicy at all.
そんなはずない、そんなはずない
That can't be, that can't be.
あ、じゃあこれみんな大丈夫かな、ちょっと
Ah, then maybe everyone will be okay.
頭おかしいだろ！
You're crazy!
なのでね、私のちょっと味覚を信じて頑張って食べていってください
So, please trust my sense of taste and do your best to eat it.
誰もしんじられないけどね！
I can't trust anyone though!
信じられるのかな？
Can we trust you?
まだ手元に来てないからわかんないんですけどね
It hasn't arrived yet, so I don't know.
はい、ということで商品説明もね、終わったところで
Okay, and so, now that the product explanation is over...
対戦に参りましょう！
Let's move on to the match!
皆様、準備はいいですか？
Everyone, are you ready?
行くぞー！
Let's go!
食わせろー！
Feed us!
実はこの企画...
Actually, this project...
はい、実はこの中に一人だけ辛くないものが配られています
Yes, actually, only one of these contains a non-spicy dish.
皆さん誰が辛くないの食べてるか考えてみてくださいね
Everyone, please try to figure out who is eating the non-spicy one.
運ばれてきました〜
It's been brought in!
なるほど？
I see?
どうですかね、皆さん
How is it, everyone?
印象はどうですか？皆さん
What are your impressions, everyone?
いや、めちゃめちゃ普通に辛そう
Wow, it looks very normally spicy.
あの、ドロドロしてますね
Um, it's gooey.
ドロドロしてる！
It's gooey!
ドロドロしてる感じかなあ、なんか色は…
It feels gooey, the color is...
やばい、なんかもう目が「見ちゃダメ！」って言ってる
It's bad, my eyes are already saying "Don't look!"
確かに。でも匂いは…
True. But the smell is...
あーすごい！でも辛そうな匂い
Ah, amazing! But it smells spicy.
めっちゃいい匂いする！
It smells really good!
目が痛い！目が痛い！
My eyes hurt! My eyes hurt!
はい、ということで皆さんのところにね、商品が揃ったところで
Okay, and so, now that the dishes are all gathered at your places...
早速？
Without further ado?
食べてまいりましょう！
Let's eat!
激辛選手権スタート！
Extreme Spicy Championship, start!
えーちゃんから、食べていただきましょう
A-chan, please eat first.
いや、辛そうですよ、これはちょっと
Wow, it looks spicy, this is a bit...
さっさと食えよー！
Eat it already!
でも全然大丈夫だからね、辛いの
But I'm totally fine with spicy things.
あ、本当ですか？
Oh, really?
あーん…
Ahh...
どうかな？
How is it?
んー！おいしい！
Mmm! Delicious!
美味しい！？
Delicious!?
ちゃんと辛味もあって、なんというか
It definitely has spiciness, and how should I say...
ちょっと濃いめの辛さとマッチして、ご飯食べたくなりますね
The slightly rich spiciness matches well, it makes me want to eat rice.
あー、確かに。ご飯食べたくなる色してるわ
Ah, true. It has the color that makes you want to eat rice.
じゃあ続いて、辛いの苦手なラプちゃん行ってみようか
Now next, let's have La-chan, who's not good with spicy food, try it.
バケモノ2が隣にいるからさ、ちょっと
There are two monsters next to me, so...
大丈夫、大丈夫。私を信じて
It's okay, it's okay. Trust me.
お前一番信じられないよ、この辛いものの場合
You're the one I trust the least when it comes to this spicy stuff.
いただきます
Let's eat.
はい…
Yes...
あ、やばい！痛い！うわぁー！
Ah, it's bad! It hurts! Waaah!
あー痛い！痛い！
Ah, it hurts! It hurts!
口に入れたとたん痛いね
It hurts the moment you put it in your mouth.
大げさ、大げさですよちょっと！
Exaggeration, you're exaggerating a bit!
牛乳！牛乳！
Milk! Milk!
本当にそんな辛い？
Is it really that spicy?
放送事故、放送事故！
Broadcasting accident, broadcasting accident!
お披露目でそれはまずい！
That's bad for a 3D debut!
ちょっと、じゃあ吐かれる前にフブキ先輩…
Wait, then before she throws up, Fubuki-senpai...
はーい！
Yes!
行ってみましょう！
Let's go!
いただきまーす
Let's eat.
本当にそんな辛いのかな？
Is it really that spicy?
涙出てきた…
Tears came out...
あーでも辛いね
Ah, but it is spicy.
おっフブキ先輩でも…
Oh, even for Fubuki-senpai...
あーでも辛ウマだ！辛ウマ！
Ah, but it's spicy-delicious! Spicy-delicious!
辛ウマ分かります！
I understand spicy-delicious!
え、でもバケモノ3だよね？
Wait, but she's Monster 3, right?
全然食べれる。あーでも全然辛いけど食べれる！
I can totally eat it. Ah, but it's totally spicy, but I can eat it!
コクがありますよね？
It has body, doesn't it?
ねーすごい美味しい。あーご飯欲しくなりますねこれは
Right? It's really delicious. Ah, this makes me want rice.
ご飯欲しくなりますね これは
This really makes you want some rice.
ヤバい、人選間違えた 1人週間間違えた!
Oh no, I chose the wrong people. I messed up for a week!
辛いですね～
It's spicy, isn't it~
では、
Now then,
子どもカレー好きの アキロゼ先輩どうぞ
Akirose-senpai, who loves child-friendly curry, please go ahead.
お願いしまーす
Here I go~
よくスープに浸してね…
Soak it well in the soup...
いただきます…
Let's eat...
ちょっと喉に!
It got in my throat a bit!
あ! 今来た 今来た!
Ah! It's hitting me now, it's hitting me!
くちびるに全部汁が付きました～!
The sauce got all over my lips~!
牛乳は没収しときます
I'm confiscating the milk.
ダメーーー!!! わたしのーーー!!!
Nooo!!! Mine!!!
時間差ありますよね、時間差
There's a time lag, isn't there?
さあ、どんどん皆さん食べていただいて
Now then, everyone, please keep eating.
ヤバい…ヨダレいっぱい出てくる…
Oh no... so much drool is coming out...
3Dお披露目でなんか言ってる
She's saying something at her 3D debut.
箸がでも進んでるのが
But the chopsticks are moving...
えーちゃんが… 半分ぐらいもう食べました!
A-chan has... already eaten about half!
結構食べてる
She's eating quite a lot.
えーはやい!
A-chan is fast!
え、でもラブちゃんより早く食べよ
Eh, but I'll eat faster than Labu-chan.
うるさい
Shut up.
でもフブキ先輩もはやーい!
But Fubuki-senpai is also fast!
ちょまてちょまてちょまて
Wait wait wait.
一番遅いのが、ラプラス
The slowest one is La+.
もう無理だって…え?
I can't anymore... eh?
どう? これあげるよ、えーちゃん
How's this? I'll give this to you, A-chan.
あげるの、ダメだよ?
Giving it away is not allowed, you know?
100万円貰えなくていいのか、お前
Don't you want to get the 1 million yen, you?
やだ!!
No!!
うっ…うぅ、現金!
Ugh... cash!
頑張れ頑張れ!
Good luck, good luck!
からあーーい!!
It's spiiiicy!!
白菜とかが凄く染みてて辛い、みたいな事前情報がありますので
We have prior information that the Chinese cabbage is really soaked and spicy.
ぜひぜひね、白菜も食べていただいて
By all means, please eat the cabbage too.
マジで痛い……
It really hurts...
白菜…あ、あった…
Cabbage... ah, found it...
ヤバい、これヤバい 応援されないと食べらんない
Oh no, this is bad. I can't eat it without being cheered on.
これ10辛なんですもんね、10辛
This is level 10 spicy, right? Level 10.
そうこれ、10辛なんだよ
Yeah, this is level 10 spicy.
10辛が一番辛いんですよね
Level 10 is the spiciest, right?
アキロゼ先輩、もう無言になってる…
Akirose-senpai has gone silent...
幹部ーー!!
Officer!!
はい、どうしたの?
Yes, what is it?
応援して…
Cheer for me...
あ、応援応援 頑張れ頑張れ頑張れ!!
Ah, cheering, cheering. Go go go!!
応援されないと食べらんない
I can't eat it without being cheered on.
頑張れ!
Good luck!
あとでハンバーグ作ってあげるから 頑張れ頑張れ!
I'll make you a hamburger later, so go go!
これ飲み込む時痛くないんで…
It doesn't hurt when swallowing...
いま喋っててもいてーよ!! これ
It hurts even now when I'm talking!! This.
え!? えーちゃんが! 早い!
Eh!? A-chan is fast!
あと…ふたくちぐらい!
About... two bites left!
やったやったー
Yay yay!
交換しよ交換しよ交換しよ!
Let's swap, let's swap, let's swap!
ダメダメダメ!! 不正不正!
No no no!! That's cheating, cheating!
主催が不正してどうするんですか
What is the host doing cheating?
見なかったことにして!
Pretend you didn't see that!
なんか……アキロゼがなんかやたら食えてるのがおかしいんだよな…
Something's... it's strange that Akirose is eating so much...
食べてます? アキさん
Are you eating? Aki-san.
でも、これ美味しいから、イケるかもしれない
But this is delicious, so I might be able to do it.
ズルしてるだろ絶対!
You're definitely cheating!
嘘じゃん! アキロゼさん我輩に嘘ついたんだ!
No way! Akirose-san lied to me!
辛い、これ… 辛い!!!!!! これ辛い!
Spicy, this is... spicy!!!!!! This is spicy!
なんかリアクションが薄いよね…?
The reaction is a bit weak, isn't it...?
うっ…辛い辛い!!
Ugh... spicy, spicy!!
アキロゼさんさ…ちょっとさ もし辛かったらどうするの?
Akirose-san... just saying, if it's spicy, what will you do?
なんか見た目どんな感じ? 見た目見せろよ!
What does it look like? Show me!
おーい!! やめろよ!
Hey!! Stop it!
やめろ!! あーー!!
Stop!! Aaah!!
おい! 明らかに茶色いだろこれ!
Hey! This is clearly brown!
ちょ、我輩の見てよ! 真っ赤! 真っ赤だよ!
Look at mine! Bright red! It's bright red!
ちょっきききき 嘘うそうそ…?
Wait, wait, wait... no way...?
全然ちげーだろうが!
It's totally different!
え!? 嘘ーー!?
Eh!? No way!?
キムチとカレーぐらい差あるけど!!
The difference is like kimchi and curry!!
ぜんぜん違うけど!
It's completely different!
アキちゃんそれ激辛? ホントに
Aki-chan, is that super spicy? Really?
ちょっとじゃあ味がね気になると思いますので
I think you're curious about the taste, so
アキロゼ先輩が食べていたものを 持ってきてもらってもいいですか?
could someone bring what Akirose-senpai was eating?
同じのを用意させていただきましたので じゃあこれちょっとラブ 食べてもらって
We have the same one prepared. So, Lapu, try eating this.
色どうですか? 色
How's the color? The color.
明らかにさ……なんか… 茶色いね
Clearly... it's... brown.
茶色い……ほら、みて
Brown... look, see.
ホントだー 別物じゃないですか!
It's true! Isn't it a different thing!
別物やんけ!
It's a different thing!
食べていっすか?
Can I eat it?
では、食べてください
Then, go ahead and eat it.
なにこれ?
What is this?
辛い辛い辛い! 辛かったよ!
Spicy, spicy, spicy! It was spicy!
どうですか? お味は
How is it? The taste.
ただの豆腐やん!
It's just tofu!
美味しい豆腐
Delicious tofu.
嘘だぁて～ アキロゼさーん??
No way~ Akirose-saaan??
アキロゼ先輩、ちょっとなんか普通の お鍋が用意されちゃったみたいなので
Akirose-senpai, it seems a normal pot was prepared for you, so
他の3人と同じ お鍋を用意させていただきましたのでこちら!
we've prepared the same pot as the other three, here!
ひとりだけ別の食ってたんだけどー!
She was eating something else by herself!
明らかに色が違うね
The color is clearly different.
先ほど「同じ」って言っていたので 多分パクパクね、食べれると思いますので
Since you said it's 'the same' earlier, you should be able to eat it all up.
ぜひぜひパクパクと食べていただければなと思います
Please do eat it all up.
そうですよ! ひとくちじゃダメですよ!
That's right! One bite isn't enough!
どうぞ! 白菜の部分食べてください
Go ahead! Eat the cabbage part.
白菜の部分!?
The cabbage part!?
ちゃんとね! ちゃんとね この辺ね
Make sure to eat it! Around here.
あ、それ美味しそう
Ah, that looks delicious.
もつもつ……
Chew chew...
ちょっとあとからくるんでね、ぜひ
It'll hit you later, so go ahead.
じゃあ、いただきます
Then, I'll eat.
結構すぐ来た!
It hit me pretty fast!
ヤバい辛い!! ヤバいヤバい!
It's super spicy!! Oh no, oh no!
牛乳牛乳!
Milk, milk!
踊りだした踊りだした
She started dancing, she started dancing.
この苦しみが分かったか! アキロゼさん!
Do you understand this suffering now! Akirose-san!
ホンマや…
It's true...
(これを)ずっと食ってた!!
I was eating this the whole time!!
ね! ほら! ね! 言ったでしょ!?
See! I told you, right!?
我輩、我輩だけ「普通の人」なの!!
I, only I am a 'normal person'!!
普通の人はこうなの!
Normal people are like this!
ということで100万円は 誰の手に渡るんでしょうか?
So, who will get the 1 million yen?
あでも、えーちゃんってこと? どっちが早かったかな?
Ah, but does that mean A-chan? I wonder who was faster?
えーちゃんとフブキ先輩 どちらになるんでしょうか!?
A-chan or Fubuki-senpai, which one will it be!?
発表お願いします!
Please announce it!
誰が100万円なんて言った?
Who said anything about 1 million yen?
誰が100万円なんて言った？
あんなのは嘘だ！
That was a lie!
100万円なんて無ーいっ！！
There's no such thing as 1 million yen!!
ひっかかったー!!!
You fell for it!!!
ザコザコザコザコ... ばかー!!!!
Weaklings, weaklings... Idiots!!!!
辛いもの食べただけだよお前らは！
You guys just ate spicy food, that's all!
いやでも美味しいもの食べさせてもらったってことかじゃあ
Well, but I guess that means we got to eat something delicious then.
ちょっと反応が違うなあ...
The reaction is a bit different from what I expected...
まあ、ラプラスさん出禁ですね！今日から
Well, La+ is banned then! Starting today.
なんで!?
Why!?
すいません、じゃあ出禁で！
Excuse me, then you're banned!
私はラプラスに言わされてただけなので
I was just made to say it by La+, so...
裏切るのか!!
Are you betraying me!?
許してくださーい
Please forgive me.
じゃあルイさんしょうがないか！
Then I guess Lui-san can't be helped!
じゃあ100万円はあげないですけどバケモノっていう称号はあげます
Then I won't give you 1 million yen, but I'll give you the title of "monster".
バケモノ... うれしいのかな......
Monster... I wonder if she's happy...
嬉しくないよ、やだよそんな称号...
I'm not happy, I don't want a title like that...
じゃあ激辛三姉妹で、頑張りましょうね
Then let's do our best as the Three Spicy Sisters.
なんかやりたいですね！
I want to do something like that!
がんばろ～
Let's do our best~
やってらんねーよ！こんなの！
I can't take this anymore! Not this!
それでは、以上ホロライブ激辛選手権でした～
And that's it for the Hololive Spicy Championship~
ばいばーい！
Bye bye!
二度とやるかー！
As if I'll ever do this again!
ほら食べ終わんないと帰れないんですよ
Look, you can't go home until you finish eating.
早く巻きでお願いします
Hurry up, please speed it up.
もう食べらんないよ...
I can't eat anymore...
食べてください 頑張って
Please eat. Good luck.
じゃあ、あとは我々食べるとして、あと一口、あと最後の一口いっとこうか
Then, the rest of us will eat... One more bite, let's go for that last bite.
せーの
Ready, set...
いただきます
Let's eat.
うわああああ あああああ
Uwaaaaaa aaaaaa
しばらこ！なんだこれ！
Shibarako! What is this!
返してやる！
I'll give it back!
戻って帰ってそのまま！もうだめだ...
Go back and just like that! I'm done...
女だらけの王様ゲーム～！
The all-girl King's Game!
はい！じゃあ自己紹介するぞ～
Alright! Let's do self-introductions~
刮目せよ～！ラプラス・ダークネスでーすよろしくお願いします
Behold~! I'm La+ Darknesss, nice to meet you.
適当だな～
That was half-hearted~
ばっくばっくば～ん どうも～！インターン シャチの沙花叉クロヱで～す
Baku-baku-baaan! Hello! The intern orca, Sakamata Chloe here~
皆さんこんまっする～ ホロライブ3期生のん～脳筋！白銀ノエルです！
Everyone, Kon-muscle~! From Hololive 3rd generation, the... muscle-brain! Shirogane Noel here!
はーいこんやっぴー！ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様でーす！
Hi, Kon-yappi! It's Hololive 4th generation's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
本物だ！もうこんな感じです...
It's the real one! It's just like this...
こんねね～ ホロライブ5期生 トワ様とラブラブな桃鈴ねねでーす！
Kon-nene~! Hololive 5th generation, the one who's lovey-dovey with Towa-sama, Momosuzu Nene!
ということでですね、今回この5人で王様ゲームやりたいと思いまーす
So, I'd like to play the King's Game with these five people this time.
なんで呼ばれたの～？ そう何でか分かんね～！
Why was I called~? Yeah, I don't know why!
まあ下心と～ 下心!? 下心と...
Well, with an ulterior motive and... Ulterior motive!? With an ulterior motive and...
ちょっとなんか面白いかな、と思うメンツを集めて王様ゲームやらせようと思って
I gathered people who I thought might be interesting, and I'm going to make them play the King's Game.
王様ゲーム、やったことある人いますか？
Has anyone played the King's Game before?
やったことはないけど～ BL漫画でよく読んでるから詳しい
I haven't done it, but I read about it a lot in BL manga so I'm well-versed.
知識だけはめっちゃある 欲望じゃねーか...
I have tons of knowledge. Isn't that just desire...
まあね、王様ゲーム 言ってる我輩やったことないんですけどね！
Well, about the King's Game... actually, despite what I'm saying, I've never done it!
ないの!? 今回、初体験王様ゲームなんでね
You haven't!? This is my first time playing the King's Game, so...
でもラプラス以外が王様引けば勝ちみたいなとこあるからね
But if anyone other than La+ draws the King, it's basically a win.
なんで！みんなで引きましょう！頑張って！
Why! Let's all draw! Good luck!
王様になりたい！むしろ
I want to be the King! If anything.
安全地帯に逃げる気ですね？
You're planning to escape to the safe zone, aren't you?
我輩なりたい！王様なりたい！
I want to be it! I want to be the King!
やだ沙花叉もやりたいやりたいやりたいやりたい...
No, Sakamata also wants to do it, wants to do it...
愛と欲望の紛れるこの王様ゲームを制するのは誰だ
Who will rule this King's Game where love and desire mix?
ねえいきなり始まる！ マジでやりたくね～
Hey, it's starting all of a sudden! I really don't want to do this~
おいおいおいおい！やるぞ～
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Let's do it~
せーの 王様だーれ！
Ready, set... Who is the King!
王様誰ですか！ 王様は...
Who is the King! The King is...
ねねー!!
Nene!!
やばいやばい 怖い怖い ねね先輩か～
This is bad, bad. Scary, scary. So it's Nene-senpai~
じゃあ～ 2番の人が... ねね真ん中に立つから、ねねに... 愛の告白... してよね～！
Then... number 2... since Nene will stand in the middle now, to Nene... a confession of love... do it!
自分が得しようとしてる！ じゃあちょっと2番の人手上げて...
She's trying to benefit herself! Then, number 2, please raise your hand...
はい我輩です!!
Yes, it's me!!
うわあああ!! ふざけんなよ～
Uwaaaa!! You've got to be kidding me~
え～愛の告白ぅ～？ じゃあ行きますよ...？
Eh~ a love confession? Okay, here I go...?
辛いチキン食べたから息臭かったらごめん...
I ate spicy chicken, so sorry if my breath stinks...
愛の告白まで... 3... 2... 1...
Counting down to the confession... 3... 2... 1...
ねね、愛してるZE！
Nene, I love you!
失笑やめて... 浅い！浅いなぁ～ 何かが違うなぁ～
Stop laughing... Shallow! That's so shallow~ Something's not right~
あ、まだやれますよ！
Ah, I can still do it!
外野うるさいんだけど!! まだあります！ちょっと今の浅かった！
The bystanders are being too noisy!! There's more! The one just now was shallow!
ねねェ... 好きだよ...
Nene... I like you...
やめた方がいいよこれ～
You should stop doing this~
なんかちがーう！
Something's wrong!
羞恥を感じるな～
I feel the embarrassment...
バックハグからの告白でいいっすか？
Is a back-hug confession okay?
あ、すごいやってくれるじゃん
Oh, she's really going for it.
めっちゃやってくれるー！行きますよ？
She's really doing it! Here I go!
…ねね！！
...Nene!!
ああ！行かさない！
Ah! I won't let you go!
ラブ様が3Dになってやりたかったことこれかよ！！
Is this what you wanted to do after getting a 3D body?!
違う！逆だろ！！我輩は！！
No! It should be the other way around!! I should be!!
なんで吾輩がやんなきゃいけねえんだよー！
Why do I have to be the one doing it?!
いい気分だったな～
That felt good~
なんか普通にやけどを負っただけだった…
I just feel like I got burned...
まあ見てるこっちも結構やけどしたけどね
Well, watching it also gave us a bit of a burn.
ホントだよぉ…
Exactly...
見ないでっ！！
Don't look!!
採点するとしたら何点？今の
If you were to score that, how many points?
え、今の告白ですかぁ？
Eh, for that confession?
いや100点だろふざけんな
It's 100 points, obviously. Don't mess with me.
え、2点
Eh, 2 points.
ふざけんなよ！！
Don't mess with me!!
じゃあお前やってみろよ！吾輩に
Then you try doing it! To me!
バカ！王様ゲーム（のルール）分かれよ！
Idiot! Understand the King's Game (rules)!
違う！ヤダヤダヤダ！
No! No no no!
やってみろよ！！！
Try it!!!
いや、ダメダメダメ、吾輩がルールだから
No, no no no, I am the rule.
はいじゃあやってみて吾輩に
Alright, now try it on me.
ラプラス…
Laplus...
好きだよ。
I love you.
あ、そういうのが欲しかった！
Ah, that's what I wanted!
これだろ欲しかったのは！
This is what I wanted!
王様ゲーム破綻してるだろが！
The King's Game is breaking down!
なんでやらされたんだよ！
Why was I made to do it!
ありがとねぇー
Thanks~
ってことは今見本見せてもらったからさ～？
Since we just saw a sample...
なんで！もういいよ！！
Why! Enough already!!
そうですね～！！
Right~!!
ちょっと本物見たいな～
I want to see the real thing.
ちょっと1回だけガチなの行こうよ、ガチなの
Let's do a serious one just once.
いやーもういいって…
No, really, that's enough...
王様やぞ！王様やぞ！！
It's the King! It's the King!!
うるせえ！黙れ！！
Shut up! Be quiet!!
…行くよ
...Here I go.
ねねさん…
Nene-san...
好きだよ。
I love you.
あぁっ！いいじゃ～ん！
Ahh! That's good!
出来るじゃん！やれば～
You can do it! If you try~
良く出来まちた～！
You did well~!
うるさーーい！
Shut up!!
もういいんだよ…///
Enough already...
ねえ吾輩の企画なのにまだ得してることはひとつもない
Hey, even though it's my project, I haven't gained anything yet.
まだ始まったばっかやぞ！
It just started!
もう早く次次次～～！！
Hurry, next, next, next!!
あいっつぎつぎー！
Alright, next next!
せーの、王様だーれ！
One, two, who is the King!
なんでだよっ
Why though
ひとりおかしい人いるー！
There's one weird person!
絶対そうだって～
Definitely her~
おう、わかりやすいなー
Oh, that's obvious.
じゃあ…いいですか、皆さん？
Then... is it okay, everyone?
静粛にお願いしますね？
Please be quiet, okay?
うわうわ、なんかもうわかりやすいなー！
Whoa, it's so obvious!
さっきと違うじゃーん！
It's different from before!
じゃあちょっとあの…王様誰ですか
Then... who is the King?
はーいはいはーい！吾輩でーす！！
Yes yes yes! It's me!!
王様我輩でーす！！
The King is me!!
皆さん、はい！媚びタイムお願いしまーす
Everyone, yes! Please start the flattery time.
ちょっとこれマジで運ゲーなんですけど
This is really a game of luck.
ちょ吾輩はこの4択を外すわけにはいかないんだよね…
I can't afford to miss this 4-way choice...
いや～ちょっと当てようとしてない！？
Wait, aren't you trying to guess!?
マジ欲が出てるわ～
She's really showing her greed~
ねえ怖い怖い！
Hey, scary scary!
ねえ、選ぼうとしてるよね！？
Hey, you're trying to choose, right!?
本当に当てないでくれ！！お願い！！
Please don't guess right!! Please!!
一回だけ、一回だけちょっと開示してもらって……
Just once, let me see them just once...
開示…？
See them...?
2番
Number 2
お前ルールをぐちゃぐちゃにするなよ！
Don't mess up the rules!
ちょ2番だった人だけ…
Just the person who was Number 2...
2択になった2択になった…
It's down to two, down to two...
さあさあさあ2択だ！
Now now now, it's a 50/50!
この2択を外すわけにはいかない…！
I can't afford to miss this choice...!
王様と……
The King and...
3番が手を繋ぐ！！で散歩する！
Number 3 hold hands!! And go for a walk!
どっちだ！どっちなんだ！？
Which one! Which is it!?
3番の人は手を挙げてください！
Person with Number 3, please raise your hand!
うええええええい！！！！！
Wooooooooh!!!!!
っしやおら！！
Alright!!
っはーこいつ
Gosh, this guy.
キモいだろこれ！！
This is gross!!
今日これだけのためにこの回をやったまである
I might have done this whole stream just for this.
職権乱用王様ゲーム！！
Abuse of authority King's Game!!
やったーー！！
Yay!!
じゃあこの事務所ちょっと手を繋いで…
Then let's hold hands in this office...
手！ちょまって…消毒しようかな、一旦…
Hand! Wait... maybe I should disinfect it first...
ねえキモい！！いいよ早くやれって…
Gross!! Come on, hurry up...
正直しんどいわー
Honestly, this is tough.
ねえキモいキモい なんかニヤニヤしてる…
Gross, gross, she's grinning...
変な空気 可哀想だろ3人がおメー！！
Awkward atmosphere. Think about the other three!!
いやいや、ちょっちなもう恥ずかしいだろ！
No, really, it's embarrassing!
おいおいどうでもいい言うのやめい！
Hey, stop saying you don't care!
散歩しましょうよちょっと
Let's walk a bit.
デ…デートですね…
D... It's a date...
何見せられてんのマジで～？
What are we watching, seriously~?
今日この後どうします？
What are you doing after this?
え、この後一直線で帰るかな
Eh, I'll probably go straight home.
ツノが痛い！
The horn hurts!
ツノがさ、刺さってるから！
The horn is stabbing me!
こ…こうやって歩きます！！
I... I'll walk like this!!
ありがとうございます！！
Thank you!!
え…ちょ幸せですね！！
Eh... I'm so happy!!
あ～良かったねぇ良かったねぇ～
Ah~ good for you, good for you~
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ツノが！ツノが凄いんだよ！！
The horn! The horn is amazing!!
ツノが痛いよ…！
The horn hurts...!
皆さん、吾輩たち今日幸せになります！
Everyone, we're going to be happy today!
「吾輩たち」じゃない！「吾輩だけ」だろ！
Not "we"! Just "you", right!
このツノがやっぱり、鋭利でちょっと危ないね
This horn is sharp and a bit dangerous.
はい、よしよし…
Okay, there there...
あ！よしよししてもらえてたよ！いま！
Ah! She was getting headpats! Just now!
ああもう！よしよし、はいはい
Good grief! There there, okay okay.
ありがとうございます！！！！！
Thank you!!!!!
ちょありがとうみんな！
Thanks everyone!
よしよし～よく頑張ったな！
There there~ you did your best!
オイイイダメダメ！！ふざけんな！おい！！
Heyyy no no!! Don't mess around! Hey!!
ダメだめっすよちょっと！！
That's not allowed!!
そんなん許されませんからね！
I won't allow that!
はぁー、キツかった
Phew, that was tough.
トワも本当に申し訳ないと思ってる
Towa also feels really sorry.
いやもう, 気持ちよかったっす！！
No, that felt great!!
はいっ！じゃあ満足したんで次！
Alright! I'm satisfied, next!
次いいっすよ！もうなんかもういいっすよ！
I'm ready for the next one! I'm good!
何でもやれます いま吾輩～
I can do anything now~
お！何でもだって
Oh! Anything, she says.
うん何でもやりますよ、行きましょう～
Yeah, I'll do anything. Let's go~
はい、集まって集まって
Alright, gather round.
せーの、王様だーれ！
One, two, who is the King!
っしゃあああああああああ!!!
YEAAAAAAAH!!!
トワ先輩!?
Towa-senpai!?
えー、じゃあ…
Well, then...
1番と3番と4番が
Numbers 1, 3, and 4...
「hololive」という文字を体でつくる
will make the word "hololive" with their bodies.
はい、じゃあ1番の人ー？
Okay, who's number 1?
はーい、吾輩でーす！
Yes, it's me!
3番の人ー？
Number 3?
はーい！ねねー！
Yes! Nene!
はい、4番の人ー？
Number 4?
はーい！団長でーす！
Yes! Danchou's here!
マジで！？
Seriously!?
なんか回避する能力つけてる？
Do they have some avoidance ability?
もうさ、居るだけの人になってる…
She's just an observer now...
帰っていい？何が変なもの見せられてて可哀想ですよね！？
Can I go home? I'm being made to watch something weird, poor me!?
ガチオーディエンスだったね！
You really were just an audience member!
帰っていいですか！？
Can I go home!?
ダメダメダメ！ここから！
No no no! It starts now!
さすがに3人言えばさ、入ってくるかなと思って…
I thought if I called three people, you'd get picked...
え、3人でアルファベット8文字…
Wait, 8 letters with 3 people...
一個ずつやってく？
Should we do them one by one?
「H」は簡単じゃないすか？だって
"H" is easy, isn't it?
あ、そ、3人でHを作るっていう
Oh, right, making an H with three people.
はい、じゃあラプラス、浮けば？「浮けば？」ってヤバいでしょ
Okay, La+, why don't you float? Suggesting you float is crazy though.
そんな、浮けねーよ！
I can't float!
ワンチャンここに乗れば… あーなるほどね！
Maybe if I get on top of this... Oh, I see!
早く！「hololive」の…
Hurry! "hololive"'s...
H！
H!
オッケーオッケー、ナイス！
Okay, okay, nice!
じゃあ次、二人で！次二人で… こうやってやってください
Next, two of you! The two of you... do it like this.
団長不安だな～ｗ
Danchou looks shaky lol.
ああ、いい感じ！いい感じ！
Ah, looking good! Looking good!
「hololive」のO！O！
"hololive"'s O! O!
よしよし…
There we go...
じゃあ吾輩が寝るんで… 縦、誰かやってください
Then I'll lie down... someone else be the vertical part.
「hololive」のL！L！
"hololive"'s L! L!
はい、オッケーオッケーオッケー
Yes, okay, okay, okay.
あと次、もう一個Oをやらないと！
And next, we need another O!
じゃあ次Lなんで、誰か寝てください
Next is L, so someone lie down.
L！なんだ、早いな！
L! Wow, that was fast!
「hololive」のL！
"hololive"'s L!
え、Vちょっとムズくないっすか？
Wait, isn't V a bit tough?
体幹鍛えよう！
Strengthen your core!
「hololive」のV！いけるいけるいける！
"hololive"'s V! You can do it!
E！え、ムズくないっすか「E」…？
E! Isn't "E" really hard...?
だいぶムズい
It's pretty hard.
あ、いけてるいけてる！あ、それいいじゃない！
Ah, you're getting it! That looks good!
ラプラスがフォークだから難しいけど… これE、ほら、ほら、E！
It's hard since La+ is a fork... but this is E! Look!
「hololive」のE！いけたー！
"hololive"'s E! We did it!
何？なんか達成感があるの悔しいっすね
Why? It's frustrating that this feels like an accomplishment.
謎の達成感ありましたよ
There was a strange sense of achievement.
トワ様これがしたかったの？
Towa-sama, is this what you wanted?
トワはなんかホロライブらしいなと思いましたけどね
I just thought it felt very "hololive."
いやーそうですね、なんか「何見せられてるんだろう」は常にあるんですけど… でもいい感じでした！
Well, yeah. I always wonder what I'm watching, but that was nice!
なんかもう、絆感じましたよ
I really felt our bond there.
そうだね。なんか一致団結感はあった
True. There was a sense of unity.
やったあ！！
Yay!!
「王様ゲーム」……？
The "King's Game"...?
次誰かクロヱ、指さないと
Next time, someone has to pick Chloe.
そっか、クロヱ指さないと！
Right, we have to pick Chloe!
そーだよお！！
That's right!!
凄い回避能力があるって！
She has amazing avoidance skills!
でもこのまま帰ってもいいなって思ってて
But I was thinking I could just go home like this.
ダメダメダメ！！！なんでだよ！
No no no!!! Why would you!?
いや見るだけ見てちょっと帰ろうかなって…
No, I just wanted to watch and then head out...
じゃあお前ここに居なくていいだろうがよ
Then you don't even need to be here, do you!?
せーの、王様だーれだ！
One, two, who is the king!?
王様誰ですか！
Who's the king!?
はーい！
Me!
ちょっとまたトワになっちゃったー☆
Whoops, it's Towa again! ☆
ガチすか
Seriously?
あ、王様権譲っていただいても全然… いいですよ？
Oh, you can totally hand over the king's rights... if you want?
じゃあ、王様権渡してもよくて… はい
Well, I could hand it over... okay.
でも自分もなんかしなきゃいけないやつにしてくれるんだったらいいよ？
But only if you give an order that I have to be a part of.
いいですよ？あ、なるほどね！いいですよ。いいですよ。
That's fine. Oh, I see! That's fine.
1番が…… 沙花叉を踏んでくれる。これどうですか？
Number 1 will... step on Sakamata. How's that?
きもっ！
Gross!
え、どうですかこれ？誰ですか1番！ちょっと気になるなー！！！
Well, what do you think? Who's number 1!? I'm so curious!!!
1番の方ー？
Number 1?
スゥ…… あ！やったー！！
*Deep breath*... Ah! I did it!!
お前の趣味やんけ！
That's just your fetish!
おかしいだろ！
This is messed up!
いや早い、早い、早いよ！早いだろお前！
Whoa, wait, too fast! You're too quick!
ヤバいでしょ！
This is crazy!
え、ちょっと… どうぞどうぞ？
Um... please, go ahead?
踏んでください？
Step on me, please?
なんでお前じゃないよ！やだー！
Wait, not you! No way!
じゃ、行きます！踏んでください！
Okay, here I go! Step on me!
おうてめぇ跪けんだよ！コノヤロー！シャチ野郎がよ！
Hey you, get on your knees! You bastard! You damn orca!
エッチな3Dに仕上げやがってよ！おいおいおいおい！
Making your 3D all lewd like that! Hey, hey, hey!
エロライブが帰ってきまくっちゃっただろうがよ、コノヤロー！
"Erolive" is making a massive comeback because of you, you bastard!
最高ーーーー！！！！コノヤロー！！オラオラオラオラ！
This is the best!!!! You bastard!! Ora ora ora ora!
ありがとうございます！！
Thank you very much!!
なんなんだこれ…… 酷いなこれ……
What even is this... This is terrible...
出来れば… あの仰向けもいただきだく…
If possible... I'd like to be stepped on while facing up...
いいってもう！蹴らすなよ！
Enough already! Don't make her kick you!
出来れば仰向けも欲しいです～
I'd really like the face-up version too~
いやでもこれはさ、他にも番号はいますからね？
But wait, there are other numbers besides 1, you know?
確かに！それもあるね！
True! That's a point!
だから仰向けをね……
So, about the face-up part...
沙花叉、王様だもん！え、いいですよね？？
I'm the king! So it's okay, right??
いやこれダメですね、元々の王様の権限はトワ株主だから
No, that's no good. The original king's authority belongs to the shareholder, Towa.
お前さー！自分で自分にやればいいじゃん
Look! You should just do it to yourself.
自分で自分に罵ればいいじゃん
You should just insult yourself.
いやだよ、つまんないじゃん…
No, that's boring...
いつもの話じゃん… ねえ、いつもの話！？
That's just your daily routine... Wait, daily routine!?
え、あの王様… なんですけど…
Um, about being the king...
いやもういいよ、もういい…… OK…… すいません、あの踏んでもらいたいんですけど～！
Okay, enough already... Excuse me, I'd like to be stepped on please!
すいませ～ん！
Excuse me~!
こいつほっといてみんなでお昼ご飯食べに行きましょうよ！
Let's leave her here and all go get lunch!
いいわねいいわね！行こう行こう！
Great idea! Let's go, let's go!
ひーどーいー！！
So meeeean!!
もう満足したよね？
You're satisfied now, right?
満足～！楽しかった～！
Totally! That was fun!
いやちょっと待って待って待って！違うよね？
Hey, wait, wait, wait! This isn't right, is it?
やだーーー！！！
Nooooo!!!
お疲れ様でした！
Thanks for the hard work!
なんで、ひどい！ひどい、かえんないで！！
Why, so mean! You're mean, don't go!!
やだやだやだ... やだー...
No no no... nooo...
ひどい...
Mean...
助けてくださ～い...
Someone help me...
え～ん...
Waaaah...
え、ほんとに踏んでくれないんですか？
Eh, you're really not going to step on me?
貴方が願った幸せなど
The happiness you wished for and such
当たり前のようなものだけど
Is something that seems ordinary, but
何処にもないよと貴方は言う
You say that it's nowhere to be found
そんな世界がまた始まる
Such a world begins again
例えば、今此処に置かれた花に / 作詞・作曲：164
For example, to the flower placed here right now / Lyrics & Music: 164
今日も電車は遅れている
Today too, the train is running late
僕の予定など知りもせずに
Without even knowing my plans
欠伸を一つ二つ飲み込んで
Swallowing one or two yawns
空に咲く雲が笑っている
The clouds blooming in the sky are laughing
楽しそうに
Happily
過ぎ去って行く装いの中へ
Into the passing attire
積み上げた思い出一つとならない
Not even one of the piled-up memories remains
旅立つ貴方への舌打ちの中
Amidst the tongue-clicking directed at you who is departing
今日も変わらず世界は回る
Today too, the world continues to turn as usual
ビルの隙間から顔を覗く
Peeking out from between the buildings
お天道様が照らしている
The sun is shining down
悲しそうに風に揺られながら
Swaying sadly in the wind
道行く人は通り過ぎて行く
People on the street pass by
貴方がどれだけの痛みを抱え
How much pain you carried
背負って悩んで苦しんだのだろうか
Bearing it, worrying, and suffering, I wonder
例えば、今此処に置かれた花に
For example, to the flower placed here right now
白々しくて手を合わせる僕には解るのでしょうか
Can I, who shamelessly join my hands in prayer, truly understand?
貴方が願った幸せなど
The happiness you wished for and such
当たり前のようなものだけど
Is something that seems ordinary, but
何処にもないよと貴方は言う
You say that it's nowhere to be found
こんな世界は沈んで行く
Such a world is sinking down
過ぎ去って行く装いの中へ
Into the passing attire
積み上げた思い出一つとならない
Not even one of the piled-up memories remains
旅立つ貴方への舌打ちの中今日も...
Amidst the tongue-clicking directed at you who is departing, today too...
例えば、今此処に置かれた花に
For example, to the flowers placed here now...
も、変わらず世界は
Still, the world continues...
まわる
to turn.
えー、ここまで見てくれて、みんなありがとうございます。
Um, thank you everyone for watching up to this point.
次で最後の曲になります。
The next one will be the last song.
えっと、オリジナルの振り付けを考えたので、注目してください。
Um, I thought of an original choreography, so please pay attention to it.
ダンスを見てもらうために、ちょっと歌は販売してる音源で生歌じゃないんですけど、
To showcase the dance, the vocals are from the distributed version and not live singing, but...
その分頑張って踊るので、見てください！
I'll do my best to dance instead, so please watch!
それでは最後の曲、「合縁事変」です。
Well then, the last song: "Aien Jihen".
Can you feel "Madness"
この世界のすべて
Everything in this world
Can you feel "Galaxy"
果てを飛び越えた
Leaping beyond the ends
Glory
ハイアスかかるバイブスで 深淵より宿すパワーを tune up
With vibes that apply bias, tune up the power dwelling from the abyss
Mass て成り立っ Capital? に 一罰百戒 穿つ「理想像」
In a capital made of mass, piercing through the "ideal" with a stern warning
傷天害理 汝に二乗 乗く満たす存在意義
Violating natural laws, squaring you, the raison d'être that fills you up
In the flow そくな「ない」返し「ない」 獅子博兎 + Impact!
In the flow, no immediate return, lion tackling a rabbit + Impact!
まわりまわる多様性を 感情的なルールで縛り付け
Binding the turning diversity with emotional rules
「るせえ全く」
"Shut up, seriously!"
うねりうねる可能性で
With swelling possibilities...
すべて超えた Identity
An identity that transcended everything
Can you feel my soul
Baby, up & up now 3, 2, 1
Nothing bad happened.
案じたってまわる循環定義
A circular definition that turns even if you worry
変わらぬ真理 合縁奇縁の淀み点
The unchanging truth, the stagnation point of fate...
make it
Nothing
bad happened.
君は君 いらぬ猜疑心に暗鬼
You are you, suspicion breeds monsters in an unnecessary heart
不毛な Blow と焦らず Flow 募る鼓動で High
Don't rush with a fruitless blow, just flow, with a growing heartbeat...
up & up
...High up & up
我が道をゆく Minority あざとく Irony
Minority walking our own path, with calculated irony
ちらり見せるピュアなハート
A glimpse of a pure heart
皆殺御免
Forgive me for the massacre
夢描いてた名声赫々 人類学 抜き足差し足 tuning up
The dream of great fame, anthropology, sneaking around, tuning up
すべて解き明かす 心満たす様
Unraveling everything, satisfying the heart
その美的な知識を刺激して
Stimulating that aesthetic knowledge
私的に生きてる体も shaking up and shape up
My body living privately is also shaking up and shaping up
我が道をゆく共犯者
Accomplices on the path I walk
Are you ready to fall into deep.
かすむ視界は冥冥 響く名声 叫べ「メーデー」
The hazy vision is darkness, fame echoing, shout "Mayday!"
無垢な犠牲 足りない愛を狂わす
Innocent sacrifice, driving insufficient love mad
まわりまわる多様性を 感情的なルールで縛り付け
Binding the turning diversity with emotional rules
「るせえ全く」
"Shut up, seriously!"
うねりうねる可能性で
With swelling possibilities...
すべて超えた Identity
An identity that transcended everything
Can you feel my soul
Baby, up & up now 3, 2, 1
Nothing bad happened.
案じたってまわる循環定義
A circular definition that turns even if you worry
変わらぬ真理 合縁奇縁の淀み点
The unchanging truth, the stagnation point of fate...
make it
Nothing
bad happened.
君は君 いらぬ猜疑心に暗鬼
You are you, suspicion breeds monsters in an unnecessary heart
不毛な Blow と焦らず Flow 募る鼓動で High
Don't rush with a fruitless blow, just flow, with a growing heartbeat...
up & up
...High up & up
告知
Announcement
2022年6月9日
風真いろは 3Dお披露目
June 9, 2022
Kazama Iroha 3D Debut
2022年6月13日
沙花叉クロヱ 3Dお披露目
June 13, 2022
Sakamata Chloe 3D Debut
2022年6月16日
博衣こより 3Dお披露目
June 16, 2022
Hakui Koyori 3D Debut
2022年6月21日
鷹嶺ルイ 3Dお披露目
June 21, 2022
Takane Lui 3D Debut
2022年6月27日
ラプラス・ダークネス 3Dお披露目
June 27, 2022
La+ Darknesss 3D Debut
そして
And then...
【#SSholoX】世界征服に向けて…
【3Dアジトお披露目】 6月30日(木) 20:00~
[#SSholoX] Towards world domination...
[3D Hideout Debut] June 30th (Thu) 20:00
holoX、集合。
holoX, assemble.
刮目せよ！
Watch closely!